Oh, my God, Austin, you won!
天呐  奥斯汀  你赢了
I... What?
我... 什么
You won the poetry contest.
你赢了诗歌大赛
I did?
是吗
- You entered a poetry contest? - Yeah.
-你参加了诗歌大赛  -对
Let me see that.
给我看看
You've been writing poetry?
你有在写诗吗
I have dabbled in poetry.
略有涉足啦
"Nobody knows this little Rose."
"无人知晓这小小蔷薇"
A poem by Austin Dickinson.
奥斯汀·狄金森  作
"Nobody knows this little Rose.
"无人知晓这小小蔷薇
It might a pilgrim be.
或行朝圣之举
Did I not take it from the ways and lift it up to thee.
若我未曾摘取此芳菲将其献予与你
Only a Bee will miss it. Only a Butterfly.
唯蜂牵挂  唯蝶想念
Hastening from far journey on its breast to lie.
远行而来于其花蕊深陷
Only a Bird will wonder. Only a Breeze will sigh.
唯飞鸟疑惑  唯微风叹默
Ah Little Rose. How easy for such as thee...
怎奈娇弱蔷薇如此轻易...
to die!"
凋落"
That's really lovely.
写得真好
You wrote this?
你写的吗
Yeah.
是啊
As a matter of fact, I wrote it for Sue.
而且我还是写给苏的
- And you forgot to read the title. - Title?
-你忘了读诗名  -诗名
Yeah. I threw one on there.
是啊  上面有写
"To Mrs. Blank. With a Rose."
"一朵玫瑰  致我的那个人"
Mrs. Blank. That's you.
"那个人"  就是你
Well, congratulations, Austin.
那恭喜你  奥斯汀
Thanks, Dad.
谢谢  爸爸
This is a marked improvement from your last attempt.
比起你上次的诗作进步不少啊
Excuse me, I feel sick.
失陪一下  我不舒服